

#### INFO



295 Dinh Bo Linh street, ward district, Ho Chi Minh city, 26, Binh Thanh Vietnam



Phone:

### X

bichthoayduoc@gmail.com Phone:

### SKILLS

OFFICE COMPUTER **PRESENTATION** TEAMWORK ENGLISH

### HOBBIES







**Talking** 

# THOA NGUYEN THI BICH

# Medical representative

I am looking forward a full time job in the dynamic environment. The important is offers a greater challenges, opportunities, practice knowledge. I will use my skills in the best possitive way for achieving the company's goals and my dream to become sales manager in 3 years.

## **EXPERIENCES:**

- Advised for more 50 students in grades 12 of my high school 2013-2014
- Graduated with honors in the "Awake your power" program of Breakthrough Power Corporation
- Became typical volunteer for the green summer campaign in the university

2014-2015

- Was leader of team about 10 peoples to make a film for presenting to freshman.
- Brang the joy for over 50 children in the Mid-autumn festival.
- Took fourth place in the "tornado of chemistry" 9th of Ho Chi Minh city university of technology 2015-2016
  - Was one of collaborators of the program "Proud of
- and - Was a volunteer in the Green Run of SECC pharmaceutical industry"
  - social work club in the universty
- Led over 40 students with the leader in the green summer campaign of my university
- the - Took 2 roles in "the pharmaceutical camp", one in one knowledge contest "the Galien journey" dancer of cheerleading, group of
- Organized successfully "the pharmaceutical camp" with class pharmacy 2013 2016-2017
- Dai-ichi Life Insurance of Vietnam at Worked

2017-2018

- Taught more 3 students to improve marks and Company, Limited
  - Finished my graduation thesis with a score of 9 out learning ability
- Became pharmaceutical representative of Vitabella
- company

### **EDUCATION:**

Graduated with Bachelor's degree of pharmacy in the University of medicine and pharmacy at Ho Chi Minh city